i also think it really serves us to expand our definition of violence our current definition
and how most people see it is is very narrow violence is not only a lethal gunshot wound
to the neck it is not only graphic loud shocking things it is not only things that happen in close
proximity to you it is also the systems keeping people unhoused uneducated without health care
and without food security it is our foreign policy violence can be slow and methodical
and completely out of sight this violence is constant and a violent response to it is not
escalation my advice that i've really found by seeking it out seeking it out both from people
that are way too online and not is that you can fix your brain by getting in touch with your body
enough to know when you're stuck in fight or flight or fawn or freeze so you can regulate i freeze
absolutely when something horrible happens and now it's in my feed and every video i'm getting served
is more of that horror or takes on the horror or a meta look at the horror it freezes me you can't do
much in that state and it really affects your mental health most importantly it does prevent action
whether it be for yourself or for your community so i suggest knowing how you react in those situations
figuring out how to regulate that looks different for everybody and trust me it takes a lot of
practice but it is worth it my advice for ice agents is to get out while you can because history says the
most likely outcome is for you to be hanging by a lamppost and then your body paraded through the streets
this is false
here
you